ehobbyasia.com 2017-06-06

# Help - Privacy

### Choose a topic: 

  * Privacy Policy
  * Overview
  * The Use of Information Collected
  * Children's Privacy
  * IP Address
  * Cookies
  * Email and Newsletters
  * Security
  * Updates of Privacy Introduction
  * Contact Detail

## Privacy Policy

eHobby Asia's Privacy and Security Measure are designed to assist you-businesses, consumers and the general public-in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us, and to help you make informed decisions when using our web site and all of our related services therein.

## Overview

The privacy practice of this statement applies to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of www.ehobbyasia.com (the "Site"). By visiting these websites you agree to be bounded by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

## The Use of Information Collected

Information obtained through online registration or email is used solely for the purpose of purchases or product transactions in our company in order to process your shipments in a timely manner. We will not distribute, share or sell your information to any third parties in any ways for the protection of your privacy. We also automatically track certain information based on your shopping pattern on our websites. The information will be used for the purposes of managing and expanding our business activities and providing customer service. Occasionally, we may use the information to notify you about important changes to our Websites, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.

## Children's Privacy

If you are under 18, please visit our website with your parent's guidance. Dependency on your local law, airsoft may not be legally sold to or operated by children under 18. Please check with your local law before placing the orders.

## IP Address

The use of your IP address is to assist in diagnosing problems and administering our website. Your IP address will be stored for security purpose. We utilize state-of-the-art technology to counter check your payment address along with IP address to avoid any fraud credit card and payment submission.

## Cookies

We use data service such as "Cookies" on the shopping cart system of the Site to assist you in shopping through our online store. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. Most "Cookies" are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Sites. Most likely, we employ your "Cookies" to keep track on your shopping cart for our recognition. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve you. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

## Email and Newsletters

We email you simply for the confirmation on your order and/or communication with you about the transactions. We send newsletters through email to you periodically to announce the latest airsoft products and services. If you do not wish to receive any promotional or marketing e-mails and/or surface mail marketing letters, you may opt-out of receiving those communications by by sending us e-mail with the subject line "Unsubscribe" to or e-mail address. Also, you can simply opt-out of that subscription by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the end of the e-mail we sent to you. 

Under the Ordinance, you have the right to: 

* check whether we hold any of your personal data;
* access your personal data held by us;
* require us to correct any personal data which is inaccurate;
* ascertain our policies and practices established (from time to time) in relation to personal data and the types of personal data held by us.

If you want to access and/or correct the personal data that you have provided to us, or if you want to ascertain our policies and practices in relation to personal data and the kind of your personal data held by us, please call our customer services hotline or contact our Head of Customer Services in writing either by post or email at: 

By post :  
eHobby Asia Co.Ltd.   
Shop B1, B/F, Lai Sun Commercial Centre, 680 Cheung Sha Wan Road, Hong Kong

By email:  
sales@ehobbyasia.com

By Customer Services hotline:  
(852) 3165 1541

## Security

Our security system monitors and prevents from any unauthorized disclosure of personal information. We utilize a licensed system in supervision. When you go through checkout, all your personal information is submitted through both industry standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption to protect your confidentiality. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP.

## Updates of Privacy Introduction

Our Privacy Statements and Policy are subject to periodic review and change. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please call us on 852 3165-1541 or write to Shop B1, B/F, Lai Sun Commercial Centre, 680 Cheung Sha Wan Road, Hong Kong eHobby Asia Co.Ltd. You can also email us at sales@ehobbyasia.com.
